<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Analysis on Blog of Cricket Premee</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/categories/analysis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Analysis on Blog of Cricket Premee</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 02:56:00 +1100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/categories/analysis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>NEP vs PAK: U19 Cricket World Cup 2024 - Match Analysis</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/analysis/2024-01-25-u19-mens-cwc-2024-nepal-v-pak/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 02:56:00 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/analysis/2024-01-25-u19-mens-cwc-2024-nepal-v-pak/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;nep-vs-pak-u19-cricket-world-cup-2024---match-analysis&#34;&gt;NEP vs PAK: U19 Cricket World Cup 2024 - Match Analysis&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Nepal faced Pakistan in another challenging encounter during the U19 Cricket World Cup 2024. Here&amp;rsquo;s a detailed analysis of the game, key player performances, and what Nepal can take away from this experience.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;early-thoughts&#34;&gt;Early Thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Pakistan struggled with the new ball, starting with too many wides, which helped Nepal ease the early scoreboard pressure.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ahmad Hussain produced a stunning delivery to dismiss Arjun Kumal out of nowhere, shifting the momentum.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Aakash Tripathi fell slashing at a delivery outside off, and after his dismissal, Nepal’s scoring rate dropped as the batsmen became more circumspect.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Bipin Rawal and Dev Khanal had a positive partnership, consistently communicating and showing intent.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;match-analysis&#34;&gt;Match Analysis&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Nepal showed resilience, taking the game deep and applying pressure on Pakistan. However, Pakistan demonstrated superior batting under pressure, rotating the strike effectively with sweeps and scoops, ultimately showcasing how to avoid getting bogged down.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEP vs NZ: U19 Cricket World Cup 2024 - Match Analysis</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/analysis/2024-01-22-u19-mens-cwc-2024-nepal-v-nz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 02:56:00 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/analysis/2024-01-22-u19-mens-cwc-2024-nepal-v-nz/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;nep-vs-nz-u19-cricket-world-cup-2024---match-analysis&#34;&gt;NEP vs NZ: U19 Cricket World Cup 2024 - Match Analysis&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The U19 Cricket World Cup saw Nepal take on New Zealand in a challenging encounter. Here’s a breakdown of the game, including key moments, player performances, and lessons learned for the Nepal U19 team.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;new-zealand-innings-bowling-challenges-for-nepal&#34;&gt;New Zealand Innings: Bowling Challenges for Nepal&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Composition Issues:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Nepal fielded too few seamers, forcing them to rely on part-timer Aakash Tripathi during crucial stages. While Tripathi bowled decently, this highlighted the need for a third frontline seamer given the nature of the pitch and the game conditions.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Game Lost in the First Innings:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
