<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NEPvAFG on Blog of Cricket Premee</title>
    <link>https://cricketpremee.github.io/en/tags/nepvafg/</link>
    <description>Recent content in NEPvAFG on Blog of Cricket Premee</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 10:30:00 +1100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://cricketpremee.github.io/en/tags/nepvafg/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>NEP vs AFG: U19 Cricket World Cup 2024 - Match Review</title>
      <link>https://cricketpremee.github.io/en/blog/reviews/u19cwc2024-nepal-vs-afghanistan-match-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 10:30:00 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cricketpremee.github.io/en/blog/reviews/u19cwc2024-nepal-vs-afghanistan-match-review/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;nep-vs-afg-u19-cricket-world-cup-2024---match-review&#34;&gt;NEP vs AFG: U19 Cricket World Cup 2024 - Match Review&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Nepal edged out Afghanistan in a fiercely contested match in the U19 Cricket World Cup 2024. Here’s a detailed breakdown of the match, player performances, and key moments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.espncricinfo.com/series/icc-under-19-world-cup-2023-24-1399722/nepal-under-19s-vs-afghanistan-under-19s-12th-match-group-d-1399735/full-scorecard&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Here is the scorecard for the match from ESPN Cricinfo.&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;early-thoughts&#34;&gt;Early Thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Afghanistan won the toss and elected to bat first.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Nepal began their bowling innings with great intensity, highlighted by Akash Chand’s fiery opening spell which left Afghanistan reeling at 35/5.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Afghanistan’s lower order, particularly Ghazanfar, Naseer Khan, and Fareed Dawoodzai, counterattacked effectively, stabilizing their innings after early setbacks.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;match-summary&#34;&gt;Match Summary&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Nepal put in a commendable effort to keep Afghanistan under pressure throughout the game. However, the Afghan lower order showcased resilience, putting up a strong partnership for the ninth wicket. Nepal’s chase faltered with quick wickets early on, and despite some promising starts, they couldn’t build a sustained innings to reach the target. However, a captain’s knock from Dev Khanal and another resilient showing from the lower-order helped Nepal over the line with a scrappy but memorable win. They are into the Super Sixes with the win.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
