<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>NPL2024 on Blog of Cricket Premee</title><link>https://cricketpremee.github.io/en/tags/npl2024/</link><description>Recent content in NPL2024 on Blog of Cricket Premee</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 09:00:00 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cricketpremee.github.io/en/tags/npl2024/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Best XI of the Nepal Premier League 2024/25</title><link>https://cricketpremee.github.io/en/blog/reviews/npl-2024-best-xi/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 09:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://cricketpremee.github.io/en/blog/reviews/npl-2024-best-xi/</guid><description>&lt;p>The inaugural season of the Siddhartha Bank Nepal Premier League 2024/25 showcased stellar performances across teams. After much deliberation, here’s our &lt;strong>Best Overall XI&lt;/strong>, featuring players who excelled with their consistent displays throughout the tournament.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Key criteria&lt;/strong> for selection:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>A fieldable team with a good ratio of batsmen, bowlers, , all-rounders, and a wicketkeeper.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>No restrictions on the number of overseas players (check out &lt;a href="#best-fieldable-xi-of-npl-202425">the Best Fieldable XI&lt;/a>
 for the best XI team with 4 overseas players).&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h3 id="overall-best-xi">Overall Best XI&lt;/h3>
&lt;h4 id="1-lahiru-milantha-openerwicketkeeper-janakpur-bolts-overseas">&lt;strong>1. Lahiru Milantha (Opener/Wicketkeeper, Janakpur Bolts, overseas)&lt;/strong>&lt;/h4>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Batting:&lt;/strong> 293 runs in 10 innings, Avg 32.55, SR 130.80, HS 87&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Milantha ended the tournament as the top run scorer but his path through the tournament had peaks and troughs. He started the tournament with a bang, scoring an unbeaten 75 against the Kings. His performances trended downwards after that but he came back strong in the final with a match-winning 87 off 49 balls. As such, he narrowly edges out Andries Gous for the opener&amp;rsquo;s spot in this Best XI with the weight of his performances in the final for a winning cause for the Bolts.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Underwhelming XI of the Nepal Premier League 2024/25</title><link>https://cricketpremee.github.io/en/blog/reviews/npl-2024-underwhelming-xi/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 13:30:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://cricketpremee.github.io/en/blog/reviews/npl-2024-underwhelming-xi/</guid><description>&lt;p>The first edition of the Siddhartha Bank Nepal Premier League 2024/25 saw several players underperform relative to expectations.Below is a list of my subjective &lt;strong>Underwhelming XI&lt;/strong>, featuring players who couldn’t deliver their best this season.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Key criteria&lt;/strong> for selection of this 11 include:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>A team with 4 overseas picks, at least 1 uncapped player, at least 1 marquee player, and a fieldable mix of bowlers, wicketkeeper, and batsmen.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Underwhelming does not mean a list of worst performers, but rather players who failed to meet expectations or deliver on their potential.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h3 id="underwhelming-xi">Underwhelming XI&lt;/h3>
&lt;h4 id="1-aashutosh-ghiraiya-opener-lumbini-lions-uncapped">&lt;strong>1. Aashutosh Ghiraiya (Opener, Lumbini Lions, uncapped)&lt;/strong>&lt;/h4>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Batting:&lt;/strong> 44 runs in 6 innings, Avg 7.33, SR 62.85, HS 16&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Aashutosh Ghiraiya had a tough campaign for the Lumbini Lions in the NPL 2024/25. Known for his stellar domestic performances, especially in the Prime Minister&amp;rsquo;s Cup earlier this year, Ghiraiya struggled to find any kind of form in this tournament. His inability to provide solid starts as an opener left the Lions in a precarious position early in their innings. This disappointing performance was a far cry from the expectations set by the teams during the player draft as he was sold for the highest price for Category B players.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>