<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Best Performers on Blog of Cricket Premee</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/tags/best-performers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Best Performers on Blog of Cricket Premee</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 09:00:00 +1100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/tags/best-performers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Best XI of the Nepal Premier League 2024/25</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/reviews/npl-2024-best-xi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 09:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/reviews/npl-2024-best-xi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The inaugural season of the Siddhartha Bank Nepal Premier League 2024/25 showcased stellar performances across teams. After much deliberation, here’s our &lt;strong&gt;Best Overall XI&lt;/strong&gt;, featuring players who excelled with their consistent displays throughout the tournament.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key criteria&lt;/strong&gt; for selection:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;A fieldable team with a good ratio of batsmen, bowlers, , all-rounders, and a wicketkeeper.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;No restrictions on the number of overseas players (check out &lt;a href=&#34;#best-fieldable-xi-of-npl-202425&#34;&gt;the Best Fieldable XI&lt;/a&gt;&#xA; for the best XI team with 4 overseas players).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;overall-best-xi&#34;&gt;Overall Best XI&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;1-lahiru-milantha-openerwicketkeeper-janakpur-bolts-overseas&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Lahiru Milantha (Opener/Wicketkeeper, Janakpur Bolts, overseas)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Batting:&lt;/strong&gt; 293 runs in 10 innings, Avg 32.55, SR 130.80, HS 87&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Milantha ended the tournament as the top run scorer but his path through the tournament had peaks and troughs. He started the tournament with a bang, scoring an unbeaten 75 against the Kings. His performances trended downwards after that but he came back strong in the final with a match-winning 87 off 49 balls. As such, he narrowly edges out Andries Gous for the opener&amp;rsquo;s spot in this Best XI with the weight of his performances in the final for a winning cause for the Bolts.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
