<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NEPvIND on Blog of Cricket Premee</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/tags/nepvind/</link>
    <description>Recent content in NEPvIND on Blog of Cricket Premee</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 10:00:00 +1100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/tags/nepvind/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>NEP vs IND: U19 Cricket World Cup 2024 - Match Review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/reviews/u19cwc2024-nepal-vs-india-match-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 10:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/reviews/u19cwc2024-nepal-vs-india-match-review/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;nep-vs-ind-u19-cricket-world-cup-2024---match-review&#34;&gt;NEP vs IND: U19 Cricket World Cup 2024 - Match Review&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Nepal faced India in a tough U19 Cricket World Cup match that ultimately proved too much for the young Nepali side.&#xA;Here’s a detailed breakdown of the game, including player performances and key takeaways.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.espncricinfo.com/series/icc-under-19-world-cup-2023-24-1399722/india-under-19s-vs-nepal-under-19s-30th-match-super-sixes-group-1-1399753/full-scorecard&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Here is the scorecard for the match from ESPN Cricinfo.&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;early-thoughts&#34;&gt;Early Thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Nepal faced a daunting challenge against an in-form Indian team in the Super Sixes stage of the ICC U19 Cricket World Cup.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;India started steadily with a composed opening partnership, making the most of Nepal’s overthrows to keep the scoreboard ticking early.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Sachin Dhas, the star of the Indian innings, paced his century perfectly, taking charge of the game and leading India to a commanding total.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Nepal’s bowlers had a tough outing but showed glimpses of control during the initial powerplay and by arresting some momentum in the death overs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;match-summary&#34;&gt;Match Summary&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;India displayed their dominance, setting up a challenging target of 298 after a brilliant 116-run innings by Sachin Dhas. Nepal’s bowling unit struggled to contain the Indian middle order, with key partnership between Uday Saharan and Sachin Dhas proving pivotal.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
