<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>UnderwhelmingXI on Blog of Cricket Premee</title>
    <link>https://cricketpremee.github.io/en/tags/underwhelmingxi/</link>
    <description>Recent content in UnderwhelmingXI on Blog of Cricket Premee</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 13:30:00 +1100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://cricketpremee.github.io/en/tags/underwhelmingxi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Underwhelming XI of the Nepal Premier League 2024/25</title>
      <link>https://cricketpremee.github.io/en/blog/reviews/npl-2024-underwhelming-xi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 13:30:00 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cricketpremee.github.io/en/blog/reviews/npl-2024-underwhelming-xi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The first edition of the Siddhartha Bank Nepal Premier League 2024/25 saw several players underperform relative to expectations.Below is a list of my subjective &lt;strong&gt;Underwhelming XI&lt;/strong&gt;, featuring players who couldn’t deliver their best this season.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key criteria&lt;/strong&gt; for selection of this 11 include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;A team with 4 overseas picks, at least 1 uncapped player, at least 1 marquee player, and a fieldable mix of bowlers, wicketkeeper, and batsmen.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Underwhelming does not mean a list of worst performers, but rather players who failed to meet expectations or deliver on their potential.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;underwhelming-xi&#34;&gt;Underwhelming XI&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;1-aashutosh-ghiraiya-opener-lumbini-lions-uncapped&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Aashutosh Ghiraiya (Opener, Lumbini Lions, uncapped)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Batting:&lt;/strong&gt; 44 runs in 6 innings, Avg 7.33, SR 62.85, HS 16&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Aashutosh Ghiraiya had a tough campaign for the Lumbini Lions in the NPL 2024/25. Known for his stellar domestic performances, especially in the Prime Minister&amp;rsquo;s Cup earlier this year, Ghiraiya struggled to find any kind of form in this tournament. His inability to provide solid starts as an opener left the Lions in a precarious position early in their innings. This disappointing performance was a far cry from the expectations set by the teams during the player draft as he was sold for the highest price for Category B players.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
