<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>NEPvPAK on Blog of Cricket Premee</title><link>https://cricketpremee.github.io/en/tags/nepvpak/</link><description>Recent content in NEPvPAK on Blog of Cricket Premee</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 02:56:00 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cricketpremee.github.io/en/tags/nepvpak/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>NEP vs PAK: U19 Cricket World Cup 2024 - Match Review</title><link>https://cricketpremee.github.io/en/blog/reviews/u19cwc2024-nepal-vs-pakistan-match-review/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 02:56:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://cricketpremee.github.io/en/blog/reviews/u19cwc2024-nepal-vs-pakistan-match-review/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="nep-vs-pak-u19-cricket-world-cup-2024---match-review">NEP vs PAK: U19 Cricket World Cup 2024 - Match Review&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Nepal faced Pakistan in another challenging encounter during the U19 Cricket World Cup 2024. Here&amp;rsquo;s a detailed analysis of the game, key player performances, and what Nepal can take away from this experience.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.espncricinfo.com/series/icc-under-19-world-cup-2023-24-1399722/nepal-under-19s-vs-pakistan-under-19s-14th-match-group-d-1399737/full-scorecard" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Here is the scorecard for the match from ESPN Cricinfo.&lt;/a>
&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="early-thoughts">Early Thoughts&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Pakistan struggled with the new ball, starting with too many wides, which helped Nepal ease the early scoreboard pressure.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Ahmad Hussain produced a stunning delivery to dismiss Arjun Kumal out of nowhere, shifting the momentum.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Aakash Tripathi fell slashing at a delivery outside off, and after his dismissal, Nepal’s scoring rate dropped as the batsmen became more circumspect.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Bipin Rawal and Dev Khanal had a positive partnership, consistently communicating and showing intent.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="match-summary">Match Summary&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Nepal showed resilience, taking the game deep and applying pressure on Pakistan. However, Pakistan demonstrated superior batting under pressure, rotating the strike effectively with sweeps and scoops, ultimately showcasing how to avoid getting bogged down.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>