<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blogs on Blog of Cricket Premee</title><link>https://cricketpremee.github.io/en/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blogs on Blog of Cricket Premee</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 13:30:00 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cricketpremee.github.io/en/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Underwhelming XI of the Nepal Premier League 2024/25</title><link>https://cricketpremee.github.io/en/blog/reviews/2024-12-20-npl-s1-underwhelmingxi/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 13:30:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://cricketpremee.github.io/en/blog/reviews/2024-12-20-npl-s1-underwhelmingxi/</guid><description>&lt;p>The first edition of the Siddhartha Bank Nepal Premier League 2024/25 saw several players underperform relative to expectations.Below is a list of my subjective &lt;strong>Underwhelming XI&lt;/strong>, featuring players who couldn’t deliver their best this season.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Key criteria&lt;/strong> for selection of this 11 include:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>A team with 4 overseas picks, at least 1 uncapped player, at least 1 marquee player, and a fieldable mix of bowlers, wicketkeeper, and batsmen.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Underwhelming does not mean a list of worst performers, but rather players who failed to meet expectations or deliver on their potential.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h3 id="underwhelming-xi">Underwhelming XI&lt;/h3>
&lt;h4 id="1-aashutosh-ghiraiya-opener-lumbini-lions-uncapped">&lt;strong>1. Aashutosh Ghiraiya (Opener, Lumbini Lions, uncapped)&lt;/strong>&lt;/h4>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Batting:&lt;/strong> 44 runs in 6 innings, Avg 7.33, SR 62.85, HS 16&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Aashutosh Ghiraiya had a tough campaign for the Lumbini Lions in the NPL 2024/25. Known for his stellar domestic performances, especially in the Prime Minister&amp;rsquo;s Cup earlier this year, Ghiraiya struggled to find any kind of form in this tournament. His inability to provide solid starts as an opener left the Lions in a precarious position early in their innings. This disappointing performance was a far cry from the expectations set by the teams during the player draft as he was sold for the highest price for Category B players.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>NEP vs IND: U19 Cricket World Cup 2024 - Match Review</title><link>https://cricketpremee.github.io/en/blog/reviews/2024-02-03-u19-mens-cwc-2024-nepal-v-ind/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 10:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://cricketpremee.github.io/en/blog/reviews/2024-02-03-u19-mens-cwc-2024-nepal-v-ind/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="nep-vs-ind-u19-cricket-world-cup-2024---match-review">NEP vs IND: U19 Cricket World Cup 2024 - Match Review&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Nepal faced India in a tough U19 Cricket World Cup match that ultimately proved too much for the young Nepali side.
Here’s a detailed breakdown of the game, including player performances and key takeaways.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.espncricinfo.com/series/icc-under-19-world-cup-2023-24-1399722/india-under-19s-vs-nepal-under-19s-30th-match-super-sixes-group-1-1399753/full-scorecard" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Here is the scorecard for the match from ESPN Cricinfo.&lt;/a>
&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="early-thoughts">Early Thoughts&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Nepal faced a daunting challenge against an in-form Indian team in the Super Sixes stage of the ICC U19 Cricket World Cup.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>India started steadily with a composed opening partnership, making the most of Nepal’s overthrows to keep the scoreboard ticking early.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Sachin Dhas, the star of the Indian innings, paced his century perfectly, taking charge of the game and leading India to a commanding total.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Nepal’s bowlers had a tough outing but showed glimpses of control during the initial powerplay and by arresting some momentum in the death overs.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="match-summary">Match Summary&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>India displayed their dominance, setting up a challenging target of 298 after a brilliant 116-run innings by Sachin Dhas. Nepal’s bowling unit struggled to contain the Indian middle order, with key partnership between Uday Saharan and Sachin Dhas proving pivotal.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>NEP vs BAN: U19 Cricket World Cup 2024 - Match Review</title><link>https://cricketpremee.github.io/en/blog/reviews/2024-02-01-u19-mens-cwc-2024-nepal-v-ban/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 10:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://cricketpremee.github.io/en/blog/reviews/2024-02-01-u19-mens-cwc-2024-nepal-v-ban/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="nep-vs-ban-u19-cricket-world-cup-2024---match-analysis">NEP vs BAN: U19 Cricket World Cup 2024 - Match Analysis&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Nepal faced a formidable challenge against Bangladesh in the U19 Cricket World Cup 2024, Super Sixes round and were beaten comprehensively by the 2020 champions.
Despite an underwhelming batting display, the match had moments of brilliance and lessons to take forward. Here’s the analysis of the match, player performances, and key takeaways.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Here is the scorecard for the match from &lt;a href="https://www.espncricinfo.com/series/icc-under-19-world-cup-2023-24-1399722/bangladesh-under-19s-vs-nepal-under-19s-29th-match-super-sixes-group-1-1399752/full-scorecard" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ESPN Cricinfo&lt;/a>
.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>NEP vs AFG: U19 Cricket World Cup 2024 - Match Review</title><link>https://cricketpremee.github.io/en/blog/reviews/2024-01-27-u19-mens-cwc-2024-nepal-v-afg/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 10:30:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://cricketpremee.github.io/en/blog/reviews/2024-01-27-u19-mens-cwc-2024-nepal-v-afg/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="nep-vs-afg-u19-cricket-world-cup-2024---match-review">NEP vs AFG: U19 Cricket World Cup 2024 - Match Review&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Nepal edged out Afghanistan in a fiercely contested match in the U19 Cricket World Cup 2024. Here’s a detailed breakdown of the match, player performances, and key moments.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.espncricinfo.com/series/icc-under-19-world-cup-2023-24-1399722/nepal-under-19s-vs-afghanistan-under-19s-12th-match-group-d-1399735/full-scorecard" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Here is the scorecard for the match from ESPN Cricinfo.&lt;/a>
&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="early-thoughts">Early Thoughts&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Afghanistan won the toss and elected to bat first.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Nepal began their bowling innings with great intensity, highlighted by Akash Chand’s fiery opening spell which left Afghanistan reeling at 35/5.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Afghanistan’s lower order, particularly Ghazanfar, Naseer Khan, and Fareed Dawoodzai, counterattacked effectively, stabilizing their innings after early setbacks.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="match-summary">Match Summary&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Nepal put in a commendable effort to keep Afghanistan under pressure throughout the game. However, the Afghan lower order showcased resilience, putting up a strong partnership for the ninth wicket. Nepal’s chase faltered with quick wickets early on, and despite some promising starts, they couldn’t build a sustained innings to reach the target. However, a captain’s knock from Dev Khanal and another resilient showing from the lower-order helped Nepal over the line with a scrappy but memorable win. They are into the Super Sixes with the win.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>NEP vs PAK: U19 Cricket World Cup 2024 - Match Review</title><link>https://cricketpremee.github.io/en/blog/reviews/2024-01-25-u19-mens-cwc-2024-nepal-v-pak/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 02:56:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://cricketpremee.github.io/en/blog/reviews/2024-01-25-u19-mens-cwc-2024-nepal-v-pak/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="nep-vs-pak-u19-cricket-world-cup-2024---match-review">NEP vs PAK: U19 Cricket World Cup 2024 - Match Review&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Nepal faced Pakistan in another challenging encounter during the U19 Cricket World Cup 2024. Here&amp;rsquo;s a detailed analysis of the game, key player performances, and what Nepal can take away from this experience.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.espncricinfo.com/series/icc-under-19-world-cup-2023-24-1399722/nepal-under-19s-vs-pakistan-under-19s-14th-match-group-d-1399737/full-scorecard" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Here is the scorecard for the match from ESPN Cricinfo.&lt;/a>
&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="early-thoughts">Early Thoughts&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Pakistan struggled with the new ball, starting with too many wides, which helped Nepal ease the early scoreboard pressure.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Ahmad Hussain produced a stunning delivery to dismiss Arjun Kumal out of nowhere, shifting the momentum.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Aakash Tripathi fell slashing at a delivery outside off, and after his dismissal, Nepal’s scoring rate dropped as the batsmen became more circumspect.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Bipin Rawal and Dev Khanal had a positive partnership, consistently communicating and showing intent.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="match-summary">Match Summary&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Nepal showed resilience, taking the game deep and applying pressure on Pakistan. However, Pakistan demonstrated superior batting under pressure, rotating the strike effectively with sweeps and scoops, ultimately showcasing how to avoid getting bogged down.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>NEP vs NZ: U19 Cricket World Cup 2024 - Match Review</title><link>https://cricketpremee.github.io/en/blog/reviews/2024-01-22-u19-mens-cwc-2024-nepal-v-nz/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 02:56:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://cricketpremee.github.io/en/blog/reviews/2024-01-22-u19-mens-cwc-2024-nepal-v-nz/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="nep-vs-nz-u19-cricket-world-cup-2024---match-review">NEP vs NZ: U19 Cricket World Cup 2024 - Match Review&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>The U19 Cricket World Cup saw Nepal take on New Zealand in a challenging encounter. Here’s a breakdown of the game, including key moments, player performances, and lessons learned for the Nepal U19 team.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="new-zealand-innings-bowling-challenges-for-nepal">New Zealand Innings: Bowling Challenges for Nepal&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Team Composition Issues:&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Nepal fielded too few seamers, forcing them to rely on part-timer Aakash Tripathi during crucial stages. While Tripathi bowled decently, this highlighted the need for a third frontline seamer given the nature of the pitch and the game conditions.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Game Lost in the First Innings:&lt;/strong>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>U19 Men's CWC 2024 Squad Preview: Nepal</title><link>https://cricketpremee.github.io/en/blog/previews/2024-01-21-u19-mens-cwc-2024-nepal/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 16:48:46 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://cricketpremee.github.io/en/blog/previews/2024-01-21-u19-mens-cwc-2024-nepal/</guid><description>&lt;p>Nepal U19 team will play their first game in the U19 Cricket World Cup 2024 tomorrow. Here is a brief overview of the players in the squad. Wishing them all the best for the tournament!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In this thread 🧵, we&amp;rsquo;ll introduce you to the 15 young talents representing Nepal at the U19 Cricket World Cup. Their passion and skills are set to make a mark on the global stage! #RisingStars #NepalU19 🌟&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>